[Theme Song]
Electric Addiction
Magi
The world!
Knight
MOJO MOJO MOJO SPY
LET'S GO
This world, a riot of colors.
Truth and lies deceive our eyes.
Look with your heart.
The truth is right at the courtyard.
Hey you good or bad, truths and lies
Can't escape the gray smoke in this heart.
Take all your courage
Maybe that's how we save the world.
Mojo Mojo Mojo Spy
The Case of the Lost Voice
I'm late! I'm late!
I'm late! I'm late! I'm late!
Late! Late! Late!
It's time for the daily morning news.
Last night, two residents of this town
Mysteriously, its voice vanished.
Apparently, the town doctors have no clue about this strange illness.
So far they can't figure out the cause or treatment.
Losing one's voice overnight is truly baffling.
These two residents, before losing their voices,
had just taken part in the recording of Treasure Match.
Could it be that seeing Miss MU in person made them so excited they lost their voices?
I can only wish them good luck.
This is Tuna Town Morning News.
We'll be right back after these ads.
Uh-oh~
Hello everyone!
This is Treasure Match, the special Sunday program.
I'm the lovable Miss MU.
Miss MU, we're off to school!
Goodbye!
Late, late, late!
Is that person here to hire Uncle for a case?
De- De- Detective Chen?
So,
What can I do for you?
Three days ago,
After taking part in the recording of Treasure Match,
my most precious treasure, the fish basin,
that fish basin was mysteriously stolen.
Later, I received a call from the thief.
Let me go to the outskirts this morning
to the Misty Bamboo Grove to retrieve it
Why not notify the police?
The fish bowl is too precious to me
I must ensure it's unharmed
If the gang finds out
I notified the police...
So I'd like to ask for your help
Understood
I'll help you
Really?
Great
What's the commission fee?
That's not urgent
Misty Bamboo Grove
I need some equipment
Aren't you going to class?
[Misty Bamboo Grove, Morning]
The meeting time is almost here
Steady
Report!
Reporting to Officer Han
Thermal cameras from all angles are installed
Thank you both for lending me this high-end equipment
Fighting criminals is what the police should do
But I have a small request
I hope you can grant it
Shh, time is almost up
I'm suffocating
Looks like to be a detective
You need superhuman endurance
Hey! Anyone there?
I've arrived at the agreed spot
Mr. Robber
Where are you?
I've brought the money you asked for
Can you return my precious fish basin to me?
Please, I beg you
You can take whatever you want
My fishing rod
My fishing boat
And my little fish hat
I'll give you all of them
I only beg you
Please give back my precious fish basin
Haha, you want the fish basin?
Found them
It's two people
Dare to call the cops
Over there
On the bamboo behind the fisherman
Stop right there!
Or I'll shoot.
Catch me if you can!
Escape? Did he get away?
How dare he!
I've decided to forbid you from now on
from intervening in all case investigations.
Uncle Sima, don't be so heartless.
Jingjing,
from now on you will watch Locky Qi
step by step.
Make sure he goes to and from school on time every day,
and never again let him join case investigations.
Yes.
But Jingjing likes solving cases with Locky.
Jingjing!
You're finally on my side.
Double the daily juice supply,
plus the latest Miss MU poster.
Reporting to Uncle Sima!
I'll definitely keep a tight watch on Locky!
Traitor!
Rolling around, rolling around, tired of rolling.
Uncle Sima doesn't even know where to go investigate cases.
What case did that fisherman ask Uncle about?
At the time, I think I saw him hand Uncle a photo.
What was the picture on that photo?
Too bad I messed everything up.
Uncle won't let me join the investigation anymore.
Uncle must have locked that photo in the secret room.
I really want to go in and see it.
But Uncle always keeps the key to the secret room on him.
And now he assigned a little guard to watch me day and night.
Uncle actually gave her the key instead of me.
I'm his own nephew!
Jingjing, what are you doing?
Watching TV.
Uncle told you not to run around.
No, I won't run around.
I just wanted to ask if you want to watch Miss MU's show.
Yes, yes, yes! I don't understand that show at all.
I see. I saw you were bored downstairs, so I came specifically to tell you.
I know there's a VHS tape at home. The content is a TV show from a few days ago, hosted by Miss MU, called Treasure Match.
I wonder if you'd like to watch it?
Wow, yes, I want to!
But that tape was recorded by Uncle.
You know Uncle is very stingy.
He locks all the tapes in his own secret room.
I don't have the key.
I really can't take it out to show you
Such a pity
The show was truly wonderful
I have the key
It's really not like being lonely and alone
At times in life, there's inevitably some unhappiness
Bidding farewell to today always leaves one feeling lost
Look at tomorrow—it's waving to me on the horizon
Every day, as the sun rises and sets, time turns, and I dream more
Looking forward to every second, every moment in life
My bright eyes are sparkling
A smile facing the sunlight
Stepping quietly at the crossroads where screams echo